Samuil Kotselov

Games Development Student

Profile

An undergraduate Games Design and Development student at the University Of Greenwich, specializing in programming. Experience with using Unity, C#, Javascript and clear understanding of version control, using Git. Currently learning and trying to master Unreal Engine 5, blueprints and C++ coding at university.

Work Experience



Painter | Top Brothers' Group LTD.

April 2021 - July 2022

- Preparing painting surfaces, including removing old paint, filling holes and cracks and washing walls. Measuring the work area to calculate the time and materials required to complete the project.
- Applying paint, varnishing and other finishes, hanging wallpapers and other decorative products. Cleaning up painting tools and supplies, replacing fixtures and rearranging furniture after completing the project.



Catering and Hospitality | Brilliantine Inc.

November 2023 - Present

- Exceptional customer service, providing a positive and memorable experience for guests
- An ability to adapt to changing customer preferences, market trends, and external factors such as seasonal demand or unexpected events. Soliciting feedback from customers and using that feedback to make continuous improvements.

Contact Info

samuilkotselov@gmail.com~ Barking, London +44514932193

LinkedIn Profile: www.linkedin.com/in/samuilkotselov-5648b92b2

Click here for my portfolio

Relevant Skills

- C# programming
- Unity
- Unreal Engine 5
- Javascript
- Effective time management
- Creativity and problem solving
- Communication skills
- · Customer service

Languages

- Bulgarian (Native)
- English (C1)
- Russian (B1)

Education



High School, Secondary Foreign Language School St. Clement of Ohrid (*Blagoevgrad*, *Bulgaria*)

Sep 2010 - May 2022

Overall grade: Very good 5.36 (UK equivalent to A-Levels: B,B,B)



C1, American University in Bulgaria – English Language Institute (*Blagoevgrad, Bulgaria*)

Sep 2011 - May 2021

BCs(Hons) Games Design and Development - University Of Greenwich

Sep 2022 - Present

Experiences

AdventureX 2022 Volunteer



November 2022

- Guiding attendees to different panels and workshops
- Setting up booths and registering attendees to the event
- Adapted teamwork and adaptability as I worked with fellow volunteers

Projects

Zombie Shootout (Group Project)

Jan 2023 - April 2023 | Unity, C#, Git

- 3D top-down shooter
- Defeat all the zombies while upgrading abilities during the playthrough
- I worked on the player movement, player dash and player shooting
- Utilizes Git for version control

Cookie's Adventure

Sep 2022 - Dec 2022 | Unity, C#

- First game created at university.
- 2D platformer
- Added a double jump mechanic, extending the project spec list

It's Powdin time! (OOP Game)

Jan 2023 - April 2023 | Unity, OOP, C#

- An updated sequel to Cookie's Adventure
- 2D platformer
- I created the cat sprites and animations using Aseprite
- Added a dash mechanic that deals damage to enemies on collision
- Utilizes OOP techniques

Hobbies and Interests

- · Fitness and physical activities
- Video editing
- · Video games
- Reading comics
- Psychology